driscolls.com 2011-12-16

# Driscoll's®

Last Updated: April 24, 2009 

Driscoll’s takes the privacy of your personal information seriously and is committed to protecting your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy covers how Driscoll’s treats personally identifiable information that is collected and received at the Driscoll’s website (the “Site”) which includes driscolls.com, mydriscolls.com any successor pages thereto, and other related websites owned operated by Driscoll Strawberry Associates, Inc. (“Driscoll’s,” “we,” “us,” or “our”). 

Driscoll’s may update this policy. Driscoll’s will notify you about significant changes by placing a prominent notice on the Site on the initial page of this Policy. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes.

### 1\. WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

1.1. Driscoll’s collects some information about our online community to enable us to give credit where credit is due, improve the Site, and improve our products and services. As described below, the type of information collected and our use of that information varies depending upon your level of interaction with the Site.

1.2. This Privacy Policy does not cover how Driscoll’s treats personally identifiable information that it obtains from other sources, such as offline, on other websites, or through email communications. This Policy also does not apply to the practices of companies that Driscoll’s does not own or control, or to people that Driscoll’s does not employ or manage. 

1.3. If you are located outside the United States, please note that any information that you provide via the Site will be transferred to the United States. By using the Site, you consent to this transfer. 

### 2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

2.1. When you visit the Site, you are not anonymous. Like most Site operators, Driscoll’s automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Driscoll’s cookie information (if any), browser type, language preference, and date and time of each visitor request. Although this information is not personally identifying information in and of itself, some information (such as IP addresses) could potentially be personally identifying information when paired with other information. Driscoll’s purpose in collecting this information is to better understand how visitors to the Site use the Site thereby improving the visitors’ experience.

**2.2. Cookies.** Cookies are text information files that your browser places on your computer when you visit a website to improve your visit to the Site. We may use cookies to obtain non-personal information. We may aggregate this data to analyze the viewing habits of visitors to the Site to improve the experience and relevance, but it will not be associated with any personally identifiable data and the cookies do not extract any information from your computer. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. You need not have cookies turned on to visit this Site but doing so may ensure the most optimal customer experience while using the Site.

**2.3. Use of Personal Information.** Driscoll’s collects personal information from you, (such as your name, address, phone number, email address, etc.) only when you voluntarily provide it to us. This information may then be used to communicate with you regarding our products, services and promotions, solicit feedback via surveys, or provide you with information that you specifically requested. We will not send you unsolicited emails unless you have opted in for marketing communication or we are contacting you to follow-up on a specific request, issue, or communication you have initiated with us.

**2.4. Sharing and Disclosing Your Information.** Driscoll’s is not in the business of renting or selling personal information you provide on this Site to other people or nonaffiliated companies. Driscoll’s does share your information to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, and under the following circumstances:

  * We provide information to trusted partners who work on our behalf or with Driscoll’s under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Driscoll’s communicate with you about us. Examples of such arrangements include receiving your Customer Relation question or comment, sending and capturing survey questions and data or receiving a career applicant’s resume, application or other job related information or attachment. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We may share your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process or to otherwise cooperate with law enforcement agencies or officials, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We may share your information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to physical safety of any person, violations of Driscoll’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We may transfer information about you if Driscoll’s is acquired by or merged with another company. 

### 3\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Our Site may contain links to websites owned and operated by third parties. Any links to the websites of third parties are provided solely for your convenience and such websites are not owned or operated by Driscoll’s. Driscoll’s has no control over the privacy practices of third party websites and your activities at those website will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We assume no responsibility for the information practices of such other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices or website content of those websites. 

### 4\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

Driscoll’s uses industry standard methods to protect data transmissions. Although Driscoll’s takes appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. CHILDREN

This Site is designed for adult users and Driscoll’s does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone who has not reached the age of majority in the state or country in which he or she resides, nor does Driscoll’s intentionally allow anyone who has not reached the age of majority in the state in which he or she resides to register as a member or submit content for publication on this Site. As such, Driscoll’s strongly encourages parents to play an active role in their child’s online activity. If you are a parent and suspect that your child has provided Driscoll’s with personally identifiable information please contact us as indicated below.

### 6\. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this Site, you signify your assent to the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this Site. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes.

### 7\. TERMS OF USE

Use of the Site is governed by the Terms of Use viewable at www.driscolls.com.

### 8\. CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions related to this Privacy Policy or how your information is treated, please contact us by email at [webmaster@driscolls.com](mailto:webmaster@driscolls.com) or write to us at:

Driscoll’s   
Attn: Customer Relations—Website  
P.O. Box 50045  
Watsonville, CA 95077-5045
